http://www.tvtfcu.org/privacy-information

Our ServicesOur ServicesSavings AccountsChecking AccountsLoansCredit CardsSkip a Loan Payment24 Hour Account ManagementSwitch to TVTFCUInsuranceAdditional ServicesFee-Free ATM LocatorsFinancial ResourcesSavings RatesLoan RatesMember DiscountsLoansSavingsContact Us
You are here: Home » TVTFCU Privacy Information
Privacy Information
What does TVTFCU do with your personal information?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information.
Please read our Privacy Policy for further information.
Children's Online Privacy
The law requires parental consent to collect or use information from a child under 13. If you are a child under the age of 13, please show this to your parents/guardians and do not use the online services of this institution without verifiable parental consent pursuant to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.
What is our policy relating to former members?
If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive member, we will adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice.
Information Security and Accuracy
We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who need to know the information to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal requirements to guard your nonpublic personal information. Procedures exist to ensure that member financial information is accurate, current and complete. Our staff responds to requests to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner.
E-commerce Security
Visitors to our web site will remain anonymous. We do not collect personal identifying information about visitors to our site. When a PIN (Personal Identifying Number) is used to enter a secured area, only the member will have access to it. No employee or other member can extract the PIN after it has been entered. Our servers collect standard non-identifying information about visitors to the site, such as date and time visited, IP address, city, state and country. This information is only used to compile standard statistics on site usage.
E-mail
If a member has provided identification (such as name, address, phone number, email) via email or information request forms, the information will only be used to communicate with them to handle their request. It is not sold or transferred to other parties. All email submitted from the credit union web site is sent directly to the authorized credit union employee's email box to ensure confidentiality.
We collect members email addresses for the purpose of informing them of upcoming promotions, special offers, events and so forth. Members may unsubscribe from said emails at any time. We may also use a member’s email as a form of contact.
Web Site Links
The credit union's site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such web sites. The links are provided to assist our members with financial and membership related tasks and events. Please contact the credit union immediately if you find a linked site contains questionable content or practices.
Web Site Applications
The credit union's Loan Applications Page and Mortgage Application Sheet are secured and all information entered by the member is encrypted and emailed to a secured server. Only an authorized credit union employee can access and print the applications from the secured server to ensure confidentiality.
Go to main navigation
What would you like to do today? View Loan Rates Apply for a Loan Apply for a Visa Credit Card Apply for a Mortgage View Savings Rates Switch to TVTFCU's Free Checking Find a Fee-Free ATM Sign up for Member Emails Learn more about TVTFCU Learn How to Become a Member View our Newsletters Read about TVTFCU in the News
Quick LinksPlease Choose... Find a Fee-Free CO-OP ATM Wire Information eZCard - Visa Credit Card Account Access Scorecard Rewards Loan Calculator Member Discounts Kirby Kangaroo Club Website Credit Reports for FREE truSTAGE/CFMG Insurance Employment
See All | Contract All Home Savings Rates Loan RatesAbout Us
About UsOur MissionOur HistoryBecome a MemberMember TestimonialsCommunity InvolvementTeacher Grant Scholarship AwardTVTFCU in the NewsOur Annual ReportNewslettersOur Services
Our ServicesSavings AccountsChecking AccountsLoansCredit CardsSkip a Loan Payment24 Hour Account ManagementSwitch to TVTFCUInsuranceAdditional ServicesFee-Free ATM LocatorsFinancial ResourcesSavings RatesLoan RatesMember DiscountsLoansSavingsContact Us
